Get into the swing of things
The Overnight is a mystery, comedy film directed by Patrick Brice.
Alex, Emily, and their son, RJ, are new to Los Angeles.
A chance meeting at the park introduces them to the
mysterious Kurt, Charlotte, and Max.
A family “playdate” becomes increasingly interesting as the night goes on.
Alex, played by Adam Scott.
Emily, played by Taylor Schilling.
Kurt, played by Jason Schwartzman.
Charlotte, played by Judith Godrèche.
RJ, played by RJ Hermes.
Wade, played by Kyle Field.
The Overnight is a 2015 American sex comedy film written and directed by Patrick Brice, and
starring Adam Scott, Taylor Schilling, Jason Schwartzman, and Judith Godrèche.
The film was produced by Naomi Scott and executive produced
by Mark Duplass, Jay Duplass, and Adam Scott.
The film had its world premiere at the 2015 Sundance
Film Festival on January 23, 2015.
It was then released in a limited release on June 19, 2015, by The Orchard.
The tone is lighthearted and mind_bending.